Rin.
Yeah?
What are you gonna ask Santa for?
I still haven't decided.
If you don't hurry, it'll be too late.
He's coming from really far away.
Really?
Yeah, so what do you want the most?
Lop Ear...
What now?
needs a friend!
Good evening.
Sorry I'm so late.
No, don't worry about it.
Rin!
What's that?
It's a Christmas tree.
And this?
Just something from work.
Can we set up the tree?
Hurry, Daikichi!
Coming.
This goes at the very top, right?
Yeah.
What's wrong?
Our house doesn't have a chimney.
Santa will find a way in.
Let's unlock the door for him!
He'll be fine!
Dear Santa,
Thanks for the presents.
Rin
What's with the carrot?
It's for Mr. Reindeer.
I'm turning the lights off.
Just a little longer.
Santa will only come once you're asleep.
Really?! Then turn them off already!
Yes, ma'am.
Dear Santa,
Thanks for the presents.
Rin
I wanted to meet Santa too.
Let's eat, Rin.
Yeah.
Oh!
Mr. Reindeer said thank you.
Dear Santa